（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
（笑脸弹出）
(smiley face popping)
（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
- [Instructor] 所以推送到 hub API。
- [Instructor] So push to hub API.
让我们看一下推送到集线器 API。
Let's have a look at the push to hub API.
你需要使用你的 Hugging Face 帐户登录
You will need to be logged in with your Hugging Face account
你可以通过执行第一个单元格来做到这一点，
which you can do by executing this first cell,
或者在终端中输入 huggingface-cli login。
or by typing huggingface-cli login in a terminal.
只需输入你的用户名和密码，然后点击登录，
Just enter you username and password, then click login,
这将存储一个通知令牌
this will store a notification token
在你正在使用的机器的缓存中。
in the cache of the machine you're using.
现在，让我们对 BERT 模型进行微调
Now, let's launch a fine tuning of a BERT model
在 GLUE COLA 数据集上。
on the GLUE COLA dataset.
我们不会讨论微调代码
We won't go over the fine tuning code
因为你可以在任何变压器教程中找到它，
because you can find it in any transformer tutorial,
或通过查看下面的视频链接。
or by looking at the videos link below.
我们感兴趣的是
What interests us here is
我们如何在训练期间利用模型中心。
how we can leverage the model hub during training.
这是通过 “push_to_hub=true” 参数完成的
This is done with the "push_to_hub=true" argument
传入你的 TrainingArguments。
passed in your TrainingArguments.
这将自动上传你的模型
This will automatically upload your model
每次保存到集线器，
to the Hub each time it is saved,
所以我们案例中的每个时代。
so every epoch in our case.
这允许你从不同的机器恢复训练
This allows you to resume training from a different machine
如果当前的被打断。
if the current one gets interrupted.
该模型将在你的名称空间中更新
The model will be updated in your name space
使用你默认选择的输出目录的名称。
with the name of the output directory you picked by default.
你可以选择其他名称
You can choose another name
通过将其传递给 hub_model_id 参数。
by passing it to the hub_model_id argument.
你还可以推动你所属的组织内部
You can also push inside an organization you are a member of
通过传递完整的存储库名称，
by passing a full repository name,
以组织名称 /,
with the name of the organization/,
你要选择的型号 ID。
the model ID you want to pick.
完成后，我们就可以开始训练了，
With that done, we can just launch training,
稍等一下。
and wait a little bit.
我会从视频中缩短等待时间。
I'll cut the waiting time from the video.
请注意，模型是异步推送的，
Note that the model is pushed asynchronously,
意味着训练继续
meaning that the training continues
当你的模型上传到集线器时。
while your model is uploaded to the hub.
当你的第一次提交完成时，
When your first commit is finished,
你可以去中心检查你的模型
you can go inspect your model on the Hub
通过查看你的名称空间，
by looking inside your name space,
你会在最上面找到它。
and you'll find it at the very top.
你甚至可以开始使用它的推理小部件
You can even start playing with its inference widget
在继续训练的同时。
while it's continuing the training.
Cola 数据集让模型确定
The Cola data set tasks the model with determining
如果句子在语法上是正确的。
if the sentence is grammatically correct on that.
所以我们选择一个错误句子的例子来测试它。
So we pick an example of incorrect sentence to test it.
请注意，这需要一些时间
Note that it'll take a bit of time
在推理 API 中加载模型，
to load your model inside the inference APIs,
所以第一次尝试使用它。
so first time you try to use it.
我们将按时间从视频中删减。
We'll cut by time from the video.
标签有问题，
There is something wrong with the labels,
但我们稍后会在本视频中修复它。
but we'll fix it later in this video.
一旦你的训练结束，
Once your training is finished,
你应该和教练一起做最后一击
you should do one last push with the trainer
推到一个方法。
that pushed to a method.
这是有两个原因的。
This is for two reason.
首先，这将确保
First, this will make sure
你正在预测模型的最终版本
you are predicting the final version of your model
如果你还没有。
if you didn't already.
例如，如果你曾经保存
For instance, if you used to save
每一步策略而不是每秒，
every in step strategy instead of every second,
这将起草一张模型卡
this will draft a model card
那将是你的模型回购的登陆页面。
that will be the landing page of your model repo.
提交完成后，
Once the commit is done,
让我们回到我们的模型页面并刷新。
let's go back on our model page and refresh.
我们可以看到制图者模型卡
We can see the drafters model card
其中包括信息，
which includes information,
我们发现调整了哪一种模型。
and which one model we find tuned.
所以最终评估损失和指标，
So final evaluation loss and metric,
使用的训练超参数，
the training hyperparameter used,
中间训练结果，
the intermediate training results,
以及我们使用的框架版本
and the framework versions we used
以便其他人可以轻松地重现我们的结果。
so that other people can easily reproduce our results.
在所有这些信息之上，
On top of all that information,
培训师还包括一些解释的元数据
the trainer also included some metadata that is interpreted
通过模型云中的 Hugging Face 网站。
by the Hugging Face website in the model cloud.
你获得了一个漂亮的小部件中报告的指标的价值
You get the value of the metrics reported in a nice widget
以及带有代码的论文排行榜的链接。
as well as a link to a leaderboard with paper with code.
所以 Tensorboard runs 也被推送了
So the Tensorboard runs have also been pushed
到这份报告，我们可以看看他们
to this report, and we can look at them
直接从模型中心
directly from the model hub
通过单击训练指标子菜单。
by clicking on the training metrics sub menu.
如果你不使用 Trainer API
If you are not using the Trainer API
微调你的模型，
to fine-tune your model,
你可以使用 push_to_hub 方法
you can use a push_to_hub method
在模型上，并直接标记器。
on the model, and tokenizer directly.
让我们测试一下以修复推理小部件中的所有标签。
Let's test this to fix all labels in the inference widget.
推理小部件使用不同的标签名称
The inference widget was using different names for labels
因为我们没有注明对应
because we did not indicate the correspondence
在整数和标签名称之间。
between integer and label names.
我们可以在配置中解决这个问题
We can fix this in the configuration
通过坐在 label2id，
by sitting the label2id,
和 id2label 字段通过适当的值
and id2label fields through the proper values
将模型配置推送到集线器时。
when pushing the model config to the hub.
完成后，我们可以在网站上查看，
Once this is done, we can check on the website,
模型现在显示正确的标签。
and the model is now showing the proper label.
现在模型在集线器上，
Now that the model is on the hub,
我们可以在任何地方使用它
we can use it from anywhere
就像我们对任何其他 Transformer 模型一样
as we would any other Transformer model
使用 from_pretrained 方法
with the from_pretrained method
具有管道功能。
of with the pipeline function.
我们只需要使用集线器的标识符，
We just have to use the identifier from the hub,
我们可以看到模型配置和权重
and we can see that the model configuration and weights
以及标记化的文件会自动下载。
as well as the tokenized files are automatically downloaded.
在下一次培训中尝试 push_to_hub API
Try the push_to_hub API in the next training
轻松与世界其他地方分享你的模型。
to easily share your model with the rest of the world.
（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)